Guide to the ILR School Working Women''s Institute Files 1971-1986
ILR School Working Women''s Institute Files
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
ILR School Working Women''s Institute Files, 1971-1986
/3099
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR); Working Women's Institute
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Consists of material on women in trade unions and material for workshops and conferences.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.; Working Women's Institute.
Form and Genre Terms:
Records (documents).
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Related Collections:
/3099m: ILR School Proposal for a Working Women's Institute for Research and Education
5583/5: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5
CONTAINER LIST
- Workshops and Conferences, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Course: Women in American Labor History, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Trade Union Women's Studies; Cornell University, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Intro'd to Collective Bargaining, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Trade Union Women's Studies Rochester, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Woman's Trade Union Studies Buffalo, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- NYSSILR, 1974-1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- NYSSILR, 1974-1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Writing and Study Skills, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Trade Union Women's Studies, 1978-1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- 100 Years of Women in the Workforce, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Union Organization & Administration, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Social Behavior and Work, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Writing and Study Skills, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Working Women's Institute, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Working Women's Institute, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Working Women's Institute, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Strategies for New Health Delivery Services for Unions and Communities, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Working Women's Institute, 1980-1986 (Box 1, Folder 19)